Inventory of the American National Red Cross records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Balkan States-South Eastern Base, Constantinople Unit, 1917-1923
  - Real estate, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 129: 13
  - Restricted donations, 1920
    Box/Folder 129: 14
  - Disaster Relief Committee, minutes, 1920
    Box/Folder 129: 15
  - Feeding stations, 1921-1923 (Reel 185)
    Box/Folder 129: 16-18
  - Ration formula, 1922
    Box/Folder 129: 19-20
  - Department of Foreign Accounts, minutes of daily conferences, 1920
    Box/Folder 130: 1
  - Greek refuges, 1922-1923
    Box/Folder 130: 2
  - ARA, Russian Unit, 1922
    - Novorossisk, Correspondence, 1922
      Box/Folder 130: 3
    - Novorossisk, Telegrams to Constantinople, 1922
      Box/Folder 130: 4-7
    - Odessa, Correspondence, 1922
      Box/Folder 130: 8
    - Odessa, Telegrams to Constantinople, 1922
      Box/Folder 130: 9
    - Theodosia, telegrams to Constantinople, 1922
      Box/Folder 130: 10-11
    - Daily letters to and from London, 1922
      Box/Folder 130: 12-15
    - Daily letters to and from New York, 1922-1923 (Reel 186)
      Box/Folder 130: 16-18
    - Russian Committee in Turkey, materials concerning the evacuation of Russian refugees from Constantinople, 1922
      Box/Folder 130: 19
    - Inspection reports, 1922
      Box/Folder 130: 20-21
    - Interim reports, 1922
      Box/Folder 130: 22
    - Correspondence regarding final report, 1922
      Box/Folder 130: 23
  - Feeding reports, 1922-1923
    Box/Folder 131: 1-2
  - Evacuation reports, 1922-1921
    Box/Folder 131: 3-5
  - League of Nations/United Nations correspondence, reports, 1922-1923
    Box/Folder 131: 6
  - League of Nations/United Nations correspondence, reports, 1922-1923 (Reel 187)
    Box/Folder 131: 7-12
  - Disaster Relief Committee, 1922-1923
    Box/Folder 131: 13
  - Near East relief, 1923
    Box/Folder 131: 14
  - American Embassy, Constantinople, 1922-1923
    Box/Folder 131: 15
  - U.S. Navy, 1922-1923
    Box/Folder 131: 16
  - Russian relief organizations, 1922-1923
    Box/Folder 131: 17-18
  - Autographs of famous persons, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 131: 19
- Petrograd Children's Colony, 1917-1922, 1988
  - General, 1918-1920, 1988
    Box/Folder 132: 1
  - History of barrack no. 4, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 132: 2
  - Xenia (Kseniia) Zhukova, 1919
    Box/Folder 132: 3
  - Red Cross Steamer Yomei Maru, letters regarding the ship stay in San Francisco, 1920
    Box/Folder 132: 4
  - Civilian Relief Department, food supplies, 1919-1920 (Reel 188)
    Box/Folder 132: 5-6
  - Personnel, 1920
    Box/Folder 132: 7
  - Inspection reports, 1920
    Box/Folder 132: 8
  - Director of Civilian Relief Doremus Scudder, Western Siberia, report, 1919
    Box/Folder 132: 9
  - All Russian Provisional Government, Omsk, 1919
    Box/Folder 132: 10
  - Laundry as part of the expense, 1920
    Box/Folder 132: 11
  - North Russian Commission, office papers, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 132: 12
  - Siberian Committee, minutes of meetings of special departments, 1920
    Box/Folder 132: 13
  - Coal and wood supplies, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 132: 14
  - Finances, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 132: 15
  - Refugee children, 1920
    Box/Folder 132: 16-17. Includes photographs
  - Refugee children, 1920 (Reel 189)
    Box/Folder 132: 18-19
  - Transportation, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 133: 1
  - History reports, 1919
    Box/Folder 133: 2
  - Personnel, 1919
    Box/Folder 133: 3
  - Letters of thanks, 1919-1920.
    Box/Folder 133: 4. Includes drawings done by children ages 8-10 in Vladivostok, inspired by traditional Russian fairy tales and given as thanks to the American Red Cross
  - Children refugees, Russian Island, Second River, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 133: 5-6
  - Subdepartments, Russian Island, reports, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 133: 7-8
  - Subdepartments, Russian Island, reports, 1919-1920 (Reel 190)
    Box/Folder 133: 9-11
  - Personnel, Second River, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 133: 12
  - Civilian relief, reports, 1919
    Box/Folder 133: 13
  - Dental Clinic, Russian Island, reports, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 133: 14
  - Requisition of supplies, 1919
    Box/Folder 133: 15-16
  - Supplies and transportation, Russian Island, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 134: 1
  - Director of civilian relief Doremus Scudder, Western Siberia, reports, 1919
    Box/Folder 134: 2
  - Requisition of shoes, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 134: 3
  - Reports, correspondence, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 134: 4-5
  - Equipment and staff, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 134: 6
  - Equipment and staff, 1919-1920 (Reel 191)
    Box/Folder 124: 7-10
  - Subdepartments, Second River, reports, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 134: 11-12
  - Russian Island, correspondence, 1920
    Box/Folder 134: 13-15
  - Requisition of supplies, Second River, 1919 (Reel 192)
    Box/Folder 134: 16
  - Requisition of supplies, Russian Island, 1920
    Box/Folder 135: 1-2
  - Correspondence, Second River, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 135: 3-4
  - "Report on the Marie Asylum, the Orthodontic Hospital in Petrograd that Supplies the Soldiers from the North Sector of the Western Front", by the Committee of Orthopedic Hospitals, 1917
    Box/Folder 135: 5
  - The American Refuge, semi-annual statement, Petrograd, 1916-1917
    Box/Folder 135: 6
  - American Relief Committee, first annual report, Petrograd, 1915
    Box/Folder 135: 7
  - Supplies, Russian Island, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 135: 8-10
  - Requisitions, Russian Island and Second River, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 135: 11-12
  - Requisitions, Russian Island and Second River, 1919-1920 (Reel 193)
    Box/Folder 135 :13
  - Transfer of Russian Island Children's Colony from Vladivostok to Petrograd, reports, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 135: 14-15
  - Audit log-book, Russian Island, 1921
    Box/Folder 135: 16
  - The Red Cross Bulletin, volume I, Riga, Latvia, 1920
    Box/Folder 135: 17. Includes additional documents re the transfer of children back to Petrograd from Vladivostok, 1919-1920
  - Allen, Riley H., correspondence, 1951
    Box/Folder 135: 18. Includes Bulletin of the League of Red Cross Societies, volumes I and II, October, 1920 and March-April, 1921, Switzerland
  - Civilian Relief Department, special correspondence in regard to trip to Petrograd, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 1
  - Allen, Riley H., Chief Executive, Petrograd Children's Colony expedition, reports written while being on board the SS Yomei Maru, to R. Teusler, Commissioner, Siberian Commission, American Red Cross, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 2
  - Mail to be taken to Petrograd by request of the chief of the Vladivostok post office, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 3
  - French Consul, Vladivostok--Refusal to permit Petrograd children to land at French ports, May 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 4
  - Instructions, reports, and other documents in preparation for return trip to Petrograd, 1920 (Reel 194)
    Box/Folder 136: 5
  - Outline of proposed return of Petrograd Children's Colony by rail from Vladivostok to Petrograd, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 6. Includes map of Siberia
  - Petrograd steamers supplies, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 7
  - Newspaper clippings, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 136: 8
  - The World's Health, monthly review of the League of Red Cross Societies, Paris, September, 1925
    Box/Folder 136: 9. Includes a poster for the International Poster Competition organized by the League, 1925
  - Cables regarding the return trip, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 10-11
  - Supplies for the trip to Petrograd, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 12-13
  - League of Salvation of the Children in Petrograd, correspondence, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 14
  - Riley H. Allen, correspondence, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 15
  - Applications to accompany the colony to Petrograd, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 16
  - Provincial Government--Maritime Provincial Zemstvo, Vladivostok, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 17
  - Expenditures by Atlantic and Pacific Division, ARC for children on the Yomei Maru, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 18
  - Personnel--Return trip, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 19-20
  - Steamers, arrangements, suggestions, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 21
  - Edward W. Ryan, ARC, Commissioner to Western Russia and Baltic States, correspondence, 1920
    Box/Folder 136: 22
  - Yomei Maru, steamer, 1920-1921
    - Committee of Parents of the Siberian Children's Colony from Petrograd, Russia (Reel 195)
      Box/Folder 137: 1
    - Assignment to duty, instructions, 1920
      Box/Folder 137: 2. Includes lists of the names of the Petrograd Children's Colony on the steamer
    - Instructions on redelivery of Yomei Maru, 1920
      Box/Folder 137: 3
    - Prisoners of war, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 137: 4
    - Dispensary reports, 1920
      Box/Folder 137: 5-8
    - Cables and wireless messages, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 137: 9
    - Cables and wireless messages, 1920-1921 (Reel 196)
      Box/Folder 137: 10-11
    - Russian Government customs exemptions, 1920
      Box/Folder 137: 12
    - Log of the trip by Riley H. Allen, 1920
      Box/Folder 137: 13-19
    - Log of the trip by Riley H. Allen, 1920
      Box/Folder 138: 1-2
    - Log of the trip by Riley H. Allen, 1920 (Reel 197)
      Box/Folder 138: 3-4
    - Letters, cables, reports, May 24-June 30, 1920
      Box/Folder 138: 5-6
    - Personnel contracts, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 138: 7
    - Reports of stay in San Francisco, 1920
      Box/Folder 138: 8
    - Letters, cables, reports regarding preparation for the trip, sailing and landing, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 138: 9-11
    - Letters, cables, reports regarding preparation for the trip, sailing and landing, 1920-1921 (Reel 198)
      Box/Folder 138: 12-14
    - Letters, cables, reports regarding preparation for the trip, sailing and landing, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 139: 1
    - Lists of children's names and addresses
      Box/Folder 139: 2
    - Preparation for the trip by Second River Colony, estimated cost per day the steamer is in use, 1920
      Box/Folder 139: 3
    - Letters of Petrograd children from the ARC Petrograd Children's Colony at Russian Island and Second River, Vladivostok, to their parents and relatives (translated copies), 1920
      Box/Folder 139: 5-7
    - Transportation of Petrograd children and Major A.C. Lyon, en route, 1920
      Box/Folder 139: 8
    - Facts about the Petrograd Children's Colony homeward bound expedition, report, 15-Sep-20
      Box/Folder 139: 9
    - V. Vilensky (V. Vilenskii), Special Representative of the Central Soviet Government, correspondence, 1920
      Box/Folder 139: 10
    - Major Lively, Division Manager, ARC, letter to the president of the Pedagogical Society of the Colony, 15-Mar-20
      Box/Folder 139: 11
    - Publicity, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 139: 12
    - Adoptions of children, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 139: 13
    - Correspondence, 1921
      Box/Folder 139: 14
    - Nikolay Egoroff (Nikolai Egorov), a boy from the Colony who was sent to France, correspondence, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 139: 15
    - Reports, 1920 (Reel 199)
      Box/Folder 139: 16
    - Temporary accommodation on Yomei Maru, drawings, 1920
      Box/Folder 139: 17. Includes ship's blueprint
    - Personnel, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 139: 18
    - Applications for a position, 1920
      Box/Folder 139: 19
    - Cooperation from other societies, 1920
      Box/Folder 139: 20
    - Inquiries, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 139: 21-23
    - Children on lists, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 139: 24
    - Photographs of barracks for colony, undated
      Box/Folder 139: 25
- Commission for Siberia, 1918-1920
  Since the headquarters were in Vladivostok, all offices and departments of the Commission for Siberia, unless specifically dealing with Western or Central Siberia, are listed under the Vladivostok Office, even though the scope of their administration often encompassed all of Siberia. However, subjects on general activity of the Commission for Siberia are listed separately, at the beginning. Relief to places other than Vladivostok are listed under the specific names of the cities, hospitals, etc. that received aidt
  - Civilian relief, 1919-1920
    - Field vouchers, 1919
      Box/Folder 140: 1-2
    - Field vouchers, 1919 (Reel 200)
      Box/Folder 140: 3-6
    - Field vouchers, 1919 (Reel 201)
      Box/Folder 140: 7-9
    - Field vouchers, 1919 (Reel 202)
      Box/Folder 141: 1-7
    - Field vouchers, 1919 (Reel 203)
      Box/Folder 141: 8-9
    - Labor bureau for refugees, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 141: 10-11
    - Applications for help, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 141: 12
    - Financial documents, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 141: 13
    - Russian White Army posters, 1918-1919.
      Box/Folder 141: 14-16. See also oversized box 223
  - Allied anti-typhus expedition, 1918-1920
    - General, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 142: 1-2
    - General, 1919-1920 (Reel 204)
      Box/Folder 142: 3-5
    - Anti-typhus train, General, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 142: 6-12
    - Anti-typhus train, Inventory, May 1920
      Box/Folder 142: 13
  - Original agreement signed by France, Czechoslovakia, Italy, and Great Britain, February 1919
    Box/Folder 142: 14
  - Allied Garrison, Vladivostok, Major S.I. Johnson, re ARC activities during the insurrection of, November 1919
    Box/Folder 142: 15
  - Allied Sanitary Committee, Vladivostok, minutes of meetings re typhus in Vladivostok, 1919
    Box/Folder 142: 16
  - Allied War Relief Association of Shanghai, 1919
    Box/Folder 142: 17
  - Altai District Cultural-Educational Cooperative Union, 1919 (Reel 205)
    Box/Folder 142: 18
  - American ambassador to Japan, Rolland S. Morris, 1918
    Box/Folder 142: 19
  - American consuls, 1918-1920
    - List of consular officers to Siberia, 1919
      Box/Folder 142: 20
    - Harbin, Manchuria, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 142: 21
    - Irkutsk, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 142: 22
    - Omsk, 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 142: 23
    - Vladivostok, 1920
      Box/Folder 142: 24
  - American Expeditionary Forces, 1918-1920
    - Adjutant General T.W. King, 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 142: 25
    - Daily bulletins, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 142: 26
    - Intelligence section, press, newspaper, summary, Vladivostok, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 143: 1
  - ARC, report on progress of operations, 1918-1920
    Box/Folder 143: 2
  - Chapters, 1918-1920
    - Chosen Chapter, Seoul, Korea, 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 143: 3-4
    - Hawaii Chapter, Honolulu, 1919-192
      Box/Folder 143: 5-6
    - Japan Chapter, Tokyo, 1918-1920.
      Box/Folder 143: 7-8. Includes clippings
    - Paris, France, 1920
      Box/Folder 143: 9
    - Philippines Chapter, Manila, 1918
      Box/Folder 143: 10
    - Russian Branch, undated (Reel 206)
      Box/Folder 143: 11
    - San Francisco Office, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 143: 12
    - Seattle Chapter, 1919
      Box/Folder 143: 13
    - Tientsin Chapter, China, 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 143: 14
    - Vallejo Chapter, 1919
      Box/Folder 143: 15
    - Vladivostok Chapter, 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 143: 16
    - Western Branch, Kobe, Japan, and Germany, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 143: 17-18
  - Criticism, 1920
    Box/Folder 143: 19
  - Liquidation of, 1920
    - General
      Box/Folder 143: 20-26
    - Closing Committee
      Box/Folder 143: 27-33
  - Special Commission, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 144: 1-2
  - Policy, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 144: 3
  - Irkutsk, Central Division, 1919-1920
    - General, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 144: 4
    - Civilian Relief Department, 1919
      Box/Folder 144: 5-6
    - Executive Committee, 1919 (Reel 207)
      Box/Folder 144: 7
    - Finance Committee 1919
      Box/Folder 144: 8
    - Manager, Capt. F.W. Prince, 1919
      Box/Folder 144: 9-10
    - Reports, 1919
      Box/Folder 144: 11-16
  - Salary committee, minutes, 1919
    Box/Folder 144: 17
  - Omsk, Western Division, 1918-1920
    - General, 1919 (Reel 208)
      Box/Folder 144: 18-19
    - Advisory Committee, 1919
      Box/Folder 144: 20
    - Civil Affairs Department, 1919
      Box/Folder 145: 1
    - Civilian Relief Department--Manager, Dr. Doremus Scudder, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 145: 2
    - Finance Committee, 1919
      Box/Folder 145: 3
    - Manager, Major Charles McDonald, 1919-1920.
      Box/Folder 145: 4-5. See also Tomsk--Evacuation, box 172
  - Publicity Department, 1919
    Box/Folder 145: 6
    - Reports and minutes of meetings, 1919
      Box/Folder 145: 7-9
    - Warehouse and supplies, 1919 (Reel 209)
      Box/Folder 145: 10-11
  - Vladivostok Office, 1918-1920
    - Addresses for invitations, list, 1920
      Box/Folder 145: 12
    - Administration, 1918-1920
      - General organization diagrams, 1919
        Box/Folder 145: 13
      - Heads of departments, 1918-1920
        Box/Folder 145: 14
    - Aid refused, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 145: 15
    - Camp service bulletins, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 145: 16
    - Canteen, 1919
      - General, 1919
        Box/Folder 145: 17
      - Naval barrack #7, 1919
        Box/Folder 145: 18-20
    - Civilian Relief Department, 1919-1920
      - General, 1919 (Reel 210)
        Box/Folder 146: 1
      - Budget, 1920
        Box/Folder 146: 2
      - Directors (Scudder, Gutelius, Edmonds, Davison), 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 146: 3-4
      - Reports, 1919
        Box/Folder 146: 5
      - Weekly reports, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 146: 6-7
      - Weekly reports, 1919-1920 (Reel 211)
        Box/Folder 146: 9-11
      - Artillery reports, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 146: 12
      - Children asylums and orphanages, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 146: 13-14
    - Coal miners, 1920
      Box/Folder 146: 15
    - Colony girls, 1920
      Box/Folder 147: 1-4
    - Customs house, 1920 (Reel 212)
      Box/Folder 147: 5
    - Government agencies, organizations, employees, etc., 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 147: 6-9
    - Groups and organizations, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 147: 10-12
    - Groups, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 147: 13
    - Groups, 1919-1920 (Reel 213)
      Box/Folder 147: 14-17
    - Groups, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 148: 1-2
    - Hospitals, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 148: 3-4
    - Lighthouse, 1920
      Box/Folder 148: 5
    - Loading and unloading organizations, 1920
      Box/Folder 148: 6
    - Police and militia, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 148: 7
    - Police and militia, 1919-1920 (Reel 214)
      Box/Folder 148: 8-9
    - Prisons, jails, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 148: 10
    - Railway men, 1920
      Box/Folder 148: 11
    - Schools and church groups, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 148: 12-15
    - Schools and church groups, 1919-1920 (Reel 215)
      Box/Folder 149: 1-5
    - Scouts, 1920
      Box/Folder 149: 6-7
    - Ship building units, 1919-1920 (Reel 216)
      Box/Folder 149: 8
    - State bank, 1920
      Box/Folder 149: 9
    - Distribution of clothing, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 149: 10
    - Conferences, 1919-1920
      - A. Medvedev, President of the Far Eastern Provisional Government, 25 March 1920
        Box/Folder 149: 11
      - Members of the Inter-Allied Railway Board, 8 December 1919
        Box/Folder 149: 12
      - Representatives of the Swiss-Swedish and Danish Red Cross (regarding American funds for relief of war prisoners), 22 January 1920
        Box/Folder 149: 13
    - Construction Department, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 149: 14
    - Contracts, 1920
      Box/Folder 149: 16
    - Correspondence, General, 1919
    - Correspondence, with other chapters, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 149: 17
    - Harbin, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 149: 18-19
    - Irkutsk, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 149: 20-21
    - Omsk, 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 149: 22-23
    - Omsk, 1918-1920 (Reel 217)
      Box/Folder 150: 1
    - Tomsk, 1919
      Box/Folder 150: 2
    - Washington, D.C., 1918-1920
      - General, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 150: 3-6
      - Regarding anti-typhus campaign expenses, 1919
        Box/Folder 150: 7
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous cables, 1918-1920
      - Index to cables sent to Washington, D.C., from Vladivostok, June-December, 1919
        Box/Folder 150: 8
    - Cables and radio service, 1919
      Box/Folder 150: 9
    - Tokyo, 1919
      Box/Folder 150: 10
    - Buchedu, 1919
      Box/Folder 150: 11
    - Cheliabinsk, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 150: 12-13
    - Ekaterinburg, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 150: 14-15
    - Chita, 1920
      Box/Folder 150: 16
    - Harbin, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 150: 17-19
    - Honolulu, 1919
      Box/Folder 150: 20-21
    - Irkutsk, 1919
      Box/Folder 150: 22
    - Irkutsk, 1919 (Reel 218)
      Box/Folder 150: 23-26
    - Japan, 1919
      Box/Folder 150: 27-28
    - Krasnoyarsk, 1919
      Box/Folder 150: 29-30
    - Manila, 1919
      Box/Folder 151: 1-2
    - Nikolsk, 1919
      Box/Folder 151: 3
    - Novonikolaevsk, 1919
      Box/Folder 151: 4-5
    - Omsk, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 151: 6-13
    - Omsk, 1919-1920 (Reel 219)
      Box/Folder 151: 14-16
    - Petropavlovsk, 1919
      Box/Folder 151: 17-18
    - Shanghai, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 151: 19-20
    - Major G.W. Simmons, 1919
      Box/Folder 151: 21
    - Colonel Teusler, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 151: 22-27
    - Tomsk, 1919
      Box/Folder 151: 28-29
    - Anti-typhus train, 1919
      Box/Folder 151: 30-31
    - Dental train, 1919
      Box/Folder 151: 32
    - Sanitary train no. 2, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 151: 33-34
    - Sanitary trains nos. 2, 7-17, 1918-1919 (Reel 220)
      Box/Folder 152: 1-8
    - Tumen, 1919
      Box/Folder 152: 9-10
    - Various points, 1919
      Box/Folder 152: 11-12
    - Vladivostok, 1919
      Box/Folder 152: 13-15
    - Verkhne Udinsk, 1919
      Box/Folder 152: 16
    - Verkhne Udinsk, 1919 (Reel 221)
      Box/Folder 152: 17
    - Various points, 1919
      Box/Folder 152: 18-21
    - Washington, D.C., 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 152: 22-28
    - Washington, D.C., 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 153: 1-2
    - Washington, D.C., 1918-1920 (Reel 222)
      Box/Folder 153: 3-18
    - Czechoslovak relief, inter-office file, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 153: 19
    - Dental Department, General, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 153: 20-22
    - Dental Department, General, 1918-1919 (Reel 223)
      Box/Folder 153: 23-25
    - Dental car no. 308, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 153: 26
    - Distributable supplies, 1920
      Box/Folder 153: 27
    - Distribution station and canteen, 1920
      Box/Folder 153: 28
    - Eastern Division (departmental), 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 153: 29
    - Executive Committee, 1919-1920
      - Correspondence, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 153: 30
      - Minutes of meetings, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 153: 31-33
      - Requests for appropriations, 1921
        Box/Folder 154: 1
      - Finance Committee, 1918-1921
        Box/Folder 154: 2
      - General, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 154: 3-5
      - General, 1919-1920 (Reel 224)
        Box/Folder 154: 6
      - Accounts, 1919-1920)
        Box/Folder 154: 7-8
      - Correspondence, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 154: 9
      - Minutes of meetings, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 154: 10-12
      - Complete set of financial reports prepared by headquarters, 1919-1921
        Box/Folder 154: 13-16
      - Weekly reports, 1918-1920
        Box/Folder 154: 17-18
      - Weekly reports, 1918-1920 (Reel 225)
        Box/Folder 154: 19
    - Fire Department, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 154: 20
    - Food, 1919-1920
      - General, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 154: 21
      - Minimum monthly sustenance for an adult, 1919
        Box/Folder 154: 22
      - Rationing, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 154: 23
      - Supplies, 1919
        Box/Folder 154: 24
    - Goods, Theft of, 1919
      Box/Folder 154: 25
    - Medical Department, 1919-1920
      - General, 1919
        Box/Folder 154: 26-27
      - General, 1919
        Box/Folder 155: 1
      - Anti-typhus train, 1919
        Box/Folder 155: 2-3
      - Correspondence, 1919